National Arts Club
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Scrapbooks, 1898-1940, Series 9:
  - Clippings, 1912-1940, 9.3:
    - Volume 17, 1936-1940 (Reel 4268, Frame 660-935)
Dec. 9-Jan. 7 x, 1959 Metropolitan Young Artists Show
Jan. 15-28 x, 1960 Sixty-second Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture by Members and Guest Artists
Apr. 18-May 1, 1960 Catherine Lorillard Wolfe Art Club Flower Painting Exhibition and Sale (D176:1128-1129)
June 8-29 x, 1960 Summer Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture by Members
undated * Arts and Crafts Exhibitions
undated * x Annual Exhibitions of Books of the Year
undated * Ceramic Art Exhibition
undated x Water-Oils by Charles S. Chapman, N.A.
undated x Fine Art of the Caribbean
undated x Painters of the United States, 1720-1920, from the Permanent Collection of the Fine Arts Department, International Business Machines Corp.
undated * Pottery Exhibition
undated * Traveling Exhibition of Enlarged Photographs of Sculpture and Spring Exhibition of Small Sculpture by Members of the National Sculpture Society
undated * Exhibition of Small Sculpture
undated x Modern Tapestries from Vienna
undated x Annual Open Water Color Exhibition
undated x Catherine Lorillard Wolfe Art Club, Flower Paintings Exhibition and Sale
undated * Unidentified exhibition installations
Index 2: Officers of the National Arts Club, 1899-1960
President
1899-1905: George B. Post
1905-1909: Spencer Trask
1910-1932: John G. Agar (Honorary President, 1932-1934)
1932-1937: John Robert Gregg
1937-1938: John Clyde Oswald
1938-1942: J. Frederick Talcott
1942-1947: John Robert Gregg
1948-1951: Harvey Wiley Corbett
1951-1954: Bailey B. Burritt
1954-1957: Lyon McCandless
1957-1958: Robert K. Chandler
1958-1959: Boylen Fitzgerald
1959-1967: Perry J. Walsh
Treasurer
1899-1905: Spencer Trask
1905-circa 1907: James Edward Sague
circa 1907-circa 1908: Robert H. Rucker
circa 1910-1913: Richard Welling
1914-1916: Edward D. Page
1917: Miles M. Dawson
1918: Alexander Konta
1919-1929: John Robert Gregg
1930-1933: Charles K. Carpenter
1934-c.1942: Rodney Wilcox Jones
circa 1953-?: Janet Howell
circa 1958-1959: Archibald E. Livingston
Secretary
1899-1904: Charles de Kay
1904: Frank Jewett Mather, Jr.
circa 1905: Henry M. Stegman
circa 1906-1907: Charles H. Babcock
circa 1907-circa 1908: Robert Van Iderstine
1909: R. H. Rucker
circa 1909-1918: Frederick S. Lamb
1919-circa 1936: John Clyde Oswald
circa 1937-circa 1942: W. Wellington Massee
circa 1945-circa 1948: J. Walter McSpaden
circa 1952-?a: Frederick L. Fagley
circa 1955-circa 1958: Earl B. Breeding
1958-?a: Robin T. Tait
Managing Director (later, Manager)
1899-1903: Charles de Kay
1932-?: Peter Tivnan
circa 1956-1959: John Williams
1959-?: Ara Daglian